A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
I see a snake in the sky.
What are you doing, Rachel?
Your father's waiting for us.
We need to get back home.
Did you see it, Mommy?
The snake in the sky?
I'm sure it was just a cloud, dear.
That gray one is the one I'm worried about.
We might get rain tonight.
Which cloud, Mommy?
A puppy!
Wait!
It's probably dirty, honey.
Leave it alone.
Hey, puppy, come here!
What's the matter?
You're lonely, aren't you?
Rachel?
Rachel, sweetie?
You shouldn't play with stray dogs.
Listen to what Mommy said and come away from there.
You don't want to get in trouble, do you?
What is it, Rachel?
Nothing?
Coming.
Sorry, Mommy.
Cheers.
Hey!
Hi!
Marvelous'
Thank you.
Six人目も合わさず運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっとわけは途絶びに引きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Rachel, you've been watching that for a long time
don't you think it's about time to turn it off?
always do what your mother tells you
if you're not a good girl, you'll be punished
goodnight, mommy
I'll see you tomorrow
goodnight, Rachel
don't you think Rachel's been acting a little weird today?
weird how?
I'm not sure how to explain it
she just seemed kind of off
kids are like that
they change overnight without their parents noticing
I don't think it's anything you need to worry about
she's just growing up, that's all
but
you're right
what?
what happened?
mommy, daddy, help
I saw a big scary snake
it was gonna swallow me up and eat me
make it stop
a snake
it's okay, sweetie
it was just a bad dream
there
you can sleep right here next to daddy, okay?
daddy's gonna make all those mean snakes go away
isn't that right, mommy?
right
medusa's revival
a spider and snake's fateful reunion?
quiet
class is starting
is everybody in their seat?
you had us all worried for a while there, Manka
I'm glad the spell's gone
and you're back to normal again
mm-hmm
feeling better than ever
ready for a good fight
ooh
I bet we could have a fight right now
sit down, Patty
fine, but can we at least have a party later?
a party in your honor, Maka
we can invite Krona, too, if you'd like
yeah, we'll all party together
we're missing someone right now, though
let me guess
Blackstar's in yet another fight, Tsubaki?
uh-huh
what a jerk
he goes off to fight and leaves you here?
what's the deal with that guy?
it's how he is
Blackstar's a little different from everyone else
that's all
I'd advise you to cut out the chatter
or else next time I won't hit the wall
hey, sorry I'm late
another fight?
yeah, it's cool
Miss Marie was the supervisor
and how'd it go?
I am the biggest star in this academy
obviously I won
winner or loser, you're still late for class
you can enjoy yourself out here in the hallway
damn it
I have to get stronger
what's been getting into Blackstar lately?
he's fighting so much
yeah, I know
ten fights and ten victories without using his weapon
something's up
like I told you all last week
we're going to be starting a new lesson today
so I hope you're ready
as you know
the Kishan's madness has woken the witch Arachne
and with her revival
the organization Arachnophobia
is once again active
so now it's time to learn about dual arts
it's simpler if I don't explain it in words
this lesson you'll learn by doing, not listening
some of you are slower than others
so we'll see
he was looking at us when he said that
you aren't even really embarrassed, are you?
alright, if I call your name
please step to the front of the classroom
first up we have Oxon Harbor
get down here
our newly recovered student
Maka
sweet!
with soul, of course
lastly
Blackstar, get back in here
in or out?
make up your mind already, would ya?
uh, why are you all sweaty?
I'm concerned you may destroy the classroom
if you use your weapon for this
so you're on your own
up until this point
your training in resonating souls
has been exclusively with your respective partners
but the fact of the matter is
you're still kids
a single soul resonance
likely won't be enough
against the type of enemy we're facing now
so what I'm going to teach you today
is how to work together
to resonate souls as a team
all five of us are supposed to match wavelengths?
I realize this is a new concept for you
but give it a try anyway
come after me with all you've got
already?
just like that?
bring it on
I'll dissect you all
creepy
hell yeah!
where's breakfast, mommy?
I'm hungry
yes, I know you are, dear
it'll be ready soon
there's plenty left over for seconds
it looks so yummy
I guess it was my imagination after all
this is the best mother can do
what a pathetically boring and tasteless meal
there's a spider
how did that filthy thing get in here?
go on, get out now
arachne
it didn't take her very long to notice
Rachel, what?
mommy
I'm going outside to play
hold it, Rachel
where are you going?
a good friend of mine is waiting for me
let go
wait
who are you?
you're not Rachel
what a bad mother
treating your own daughter
like she's a stranger
she's such a good little girl too
and so easily controlled
no
don't forget to lock the doors and windows
if they're open, snakes and spiders will get in
we don't want that
bye-bye, mommy
Rachel!
I have no idea how this is done
do you?
no clue
but Stein's not messing around this time
we're just going to have to figure something out
let's go
I still don't see how we're supposed to match wavelengths with these guys
but okay
die
you mad scientist wacko
for a freak
anybody else want in on the fun?
don't overthink it
it won't do you any good
I can barely think at all with this many people watching us
damn you
all right
my turn
royal thunder
you are the death wish
hey man, it's your own fault
you're the one who jumped in front of my attack
move it
maca
you damn idiot
my bad
sorry, black star
royal thunder
how pathetic
that was even worse than I'd expected
I'm done with this
professor, I'm going to beat the crap out of Ox now
will you act as fight supervisor?
save your fighting for after class
whatever you say, professor
but black star and I are going to have to settle this eventually
why do I bother?
do you think you stand a chance against the royal thunder commander?
that makes 11 straight victories for black star
but is it really a victory if your opponent was that pathetic?
I asked them to work together and they beat each other up instead
so much for that
even if we had all the time in the world
it still may not be enough
they don't seem to get it
what do you think Lord Death's reason is
for keeping the book of Abon in the vault
if he wanted us to know
he would have told us
let it go
this is Lord Death's personal collection
there's some pretty frightening stuff down here
now there's no need to be shy
go ahead and drink it up
a glass of fresh blood should do the trick
thank you
it's an honor Lady Arachne
of course it might be poisoned
I'm joking
we can't kill you quite yet
unfortunately we have to keep you around
if we want to get the book of Abon back
forgive me my lady
the plans for the magic tool were lost
because of my incompetence
you can make it up to me by doing better
next time mosquito
anyway at least one good thing came of your failure
we were able to test Mifune's abilities
yes
and I believe we'll be able to put his power to good use
is that your big plan
what good are you if that's the only thing you can come up with
I suggest you watch your tone with me
got it chainsaw boy
my chains are getting dull
maybe I should sharpen them on your body old man
just try it
I'll drain every drop of blood from your body
until you're an empty sack of skin
police stinger
yeah fly away little bug
that's all you can do
I hate to break it to you
but you're past your prime
then maybe you'd like to take a look at my form from 800 years ago
this is my three teeth police stinger
there's nothing better than reclaiming lost youth is there
shall I snap a picture for you
what do you say
of course it'll be an awkward portrait with you cut up into little bits and all
you young
lady arachne
yes what is it now
there's a guest waiting to see you
a guest who is it
forgive me lady arachne but she keeps insisting that she's your little sister
I see
very well
show her in
my my look at you
what an adorable body you found this time Medusa
how sweet that you still remember me after 800 long years
how could I forget you I always make sure to keep you in my sights no matter how many centuries pass
it seems you're still as good as by as ever arachne
you haven't changed a bit either
still barging in here without warning not showing an ounce of fear
you'll never learn will you
not even in that dreadful new form you have
oh but you can get away with a lot in this body
I find your determination truly inspiring
you were badly hurt during that fight at the academy
your soul was torn into pieces but here you stand alive and well
I knew there was one thing I had to avoid at any cost at no point could I allow Stein and Deathscythe to swallow my soul
when I took that final blow I split my soul into pieces entered a snake and repaired myself so that I could return once more
that was a dangerous move even for a powerful witch like yourself
you survived out of sheer luck
you're probably right
the revival of the Kishin Asherah caused the release of strong madness wavelengths
my magic was able to feed off of their power
it's likely I wouldn't survive that again
so what brings you here Medusa
I fought the grim reaper 800 years ago until at the very end of the battle
someone betrayed me
you think you can just drop in here and leave again without paying a price
it's silly to cling to the past like that
the two of us should be friends
we're a pair of newly revived sisters after all
how thoughtful a surprise party to welcome me back to the world
but it's so sudden and I'm afraid I'm no good at parties
I'll see you again soon though dear sister of mine
she always was an obnoxious girl
I'll see her out my lady
are you sure about her I'll let her play her games for a while
in the end she'll be caught in my web like everybody else
you can't just show up here like that whenever you want to Medusa
if you're not careful you're going to get me discovered
you'll continue surveillance as instructed as that understood Erica
yes ma'am
I thought after this she'd finally let me go
freedom always comes at a price
so uh what are you going to do now
I'm borrowing this
I have to retrieve something precious that I left behind
in Death City
I'll see you next time
Music
行けるはずだろう
穢れなく光が闇を貫いて
この時が永遠だと今命が叫んでる
この心の奥にいつも君が映るよ
守るべき真実をただ抱いてゆけ
繰り返す毎日のパロナミに飲まれても
まだ夢から覚める 俺たちはここにいる
いつも聞こえてくる 仲間たちの声が
孤独を振り払うように
街の風の中
ただ行くしかないさ
信じた生き様を
あー!
Maka here. Next week, Kid and the others get in big trouble.
Medusa here. As you can see, due to popular demand, I've returned.
I like studying.
I like experiments.
I do the maka chop.
I lie and hurt people a lot.
It may be hard to believe, but next week you'll see we have something in common.
Um, how should we put this?
Neither of us is in the next episode.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the red-hot runaway express.
A magic tool left behind by the great wizard.
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.